Guide to the New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council Records WAG.123
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: General Files, circa 1930-1989
  - Impartial Chairman: Correspondence, 1971-1984 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Impartial Chairman: Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1985 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Impartial Chairman: Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1985 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Impartial Chairman: Correspondence, Jan-May 1986 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Impartial Chairman: Correspondence, Jul 1986 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Impartial Chairman: Correspondence, Aug 1986 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Impartial Chairman: Correspondence, Sep-Dec 1986 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jan-Jul 1950 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Aug-Dec 1950 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jan-Jun 1951 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jul-Dec 1951 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jan 1952 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Feb-Jun 1952 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jul-Dec 1952 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jan-Jun 1953 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jul-Dec 1953 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jan-Jun 1954 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jul-Dec 1954 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jan-Sep 1957 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Oct-Dec1957 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jan-Jun 1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jul-Dec 1958 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jan-Jun 1964 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Impartial Chairman Decisions, Jul-Dec 1964 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Impartial Chairman: Decisions, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Impartial Chairman: Decisions, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Impartial Chairman: Decisions, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Impartial Chairman: Decisions, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Impartial Chairman: Decisions, 1977-1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Impartial Chairman: Decisions, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Impartial Chairman: Grievance Board Reports, 1966-1969 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Impartial Chairman: Peter Seitz, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Impartial Chairman: Requests for Hearings, 1959-1967 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Industries Training Fund, 1958; 1979 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Industry Training Fund: Contract, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Industry Training Fund: Financial Statements, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Industry Training Fund: Financial Statements, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Industry Training Fund: Minutes, Trustees, 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Industry Training Fund: Minutes, Trustees, 1976-1979 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Industry Training Program, 1969-1980 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Industry Training Program, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Industry Training Program: Arrears, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Industry Training Program: Brochures, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Industry Training Program: College Credit, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Industry Training Program: Correspondence, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Industry Training Program: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Industry Training Program: Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Industry Training Program: Course Outlines, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Industry Training Program: Culinary Apprenticeship Program, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Industry Training Program: Enrollment, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Industry Training Program: Financial Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Industry Training Program: Graduation Lists, 1973-1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Industry Training Program: Observation Report, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Industry Training Program: Proposals, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Industry Training Program: Sasso, Angelo, 1981-1986 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Industry Training Program: Trustees Meetings, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Industry Training Program: Trustees Meetings, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Industry Training Program: Trustees Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Industry Training Program: Vocational Education Students, Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Insurance Fund, 1955; 1964-1974 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Insurance Fund, 1981-1986 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Insurance Fund, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Insurance Fund: Annual Reports, 1947-1952 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - IBEW, Local 1005 (Telephone Operators), 1963 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - International House of Pancakes, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - JFK Americana Corp. v. HTC, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Joint Executive Board, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Jurisdiction, 1938-1958 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Katz, Jonas B., 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - King, Bill, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Koch Fundraiser, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Perulli, Francesco, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Labor Day/Solidarity Day: Expenses, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Lapidus, Dr. Paul W., 1971-1976 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Las Vegas Strike, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Lawsuits: Bristol (Golden Horn Restaurant v. Jay Rubin et. al.), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Lawsuits: Chatham (Cup and Saucer Sandwich Shop v. Herman et al.), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Lawsuits: Taft Management v. HTC, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Lawsuits: Taft (Zeckendorf Bankruptcy), 1965 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Lawsuits: Theresa., 1960 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Leaflets: General, Undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Leaflets: Early Organizing, 1930s-1950s (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Legislative, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Legislative, 1976-1983 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Legislative (U.S. Congress), 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Lie Detectors, 1962-1965 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Locals: Outside NY, 1958-1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Local 1, 1982-1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Local 1: Bargaining, 1967-1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Local 1: Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Local 1: Catering Industry Employee, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Local 1: Members Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Local 1: Miller, Ed, Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Local 1: Miller, Ed, Correspondence, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Local 1: Pinto, Stein and Mozer, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Local 18 (Guards), 1967-1971 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Local 43 (Upholsterers) and Local 1 (Carpenters), 1953-1976 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Local 56 (Firemen), 1953-1973 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Local 56 (Maintenance), 1982-1986 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Local 60 (Deli and Restaurant), 1978 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Local 89 (Chefs), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Local 94, 1942-1977 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Local 94 (Operating Engineers), 1980-1986 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Local 94: Receipts Ledger, 1943-1946 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Local 115 (Bartenders), 1978 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Local 144 (Hotel), 1983-1987 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Local 144 (Hotel, Nursing Homes), 1956-1978 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Local 144 (Hotel, Nursing Homes), 1979-1986 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Local 164 (Bartenders), 1958;1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Local 610, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Local 610, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Local 610, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Local 610, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Local 610, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Local 610, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Local 610, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Local 610, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Local 610, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Local 610, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Local 610, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Local 610, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Local 610: Agreement, Mavi Hilton Hotel and ILWU, Local 142, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Local 610: Agreement, Met Hotel Association and Local 610, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Local 610: Analysis of Puerto Rican Hotel Industry, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Local 610: Bylaws, Puerto Rico, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Local 610: Clippings, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Local 610: Correspondence, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Local 610: Correspondence, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Local 610: Correspondence, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Local 610: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Local 610: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Local 610: Health Benefits, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Local 610: History in Spanish, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Local 610: Reports to International, 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Local 610: Welfare Plan, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Local 1005 (Telephone), 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Local 1005 (Telephone), 1954-1976 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Local 1422 (Painters), 1954-1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Loew's Hotels, Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Loyalty Oaths, 1962-1970 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Maids: Room Quotas, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Maids: Wage Parity, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Management Reports, Taft Hotels, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Marriott, 1978-1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Martin Segal and Co., 1977-1981 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Meal Allowance, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Meal Valuation (For Tax), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Medical Clinics: Guidotte Study (Vol 1), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Medical Clinics: Guidotte Study (Vol II), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Medical Clinics: Guidotte Study (Vol III), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Medical FuUndated, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Merger, 1979-1983 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Miami Strike, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Midtown: Planning, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Minimum Wage, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Minimum Wage, 1960-1966 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Minimum Wage, 1968-1972 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Minimum Wage: Federal, 1960-1966 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Minimum Wage: State, 1947-1953 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Minimum Wage: State, 1954-1967 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Minimum Wage Board: Minutes, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Mozer and Gulmy, 1978-1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - National Health Insurance, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB): Binter Food Corps. v. RWDSU, Local 923, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - NLRB Cases, 1971-1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - NLRB: Moreno v. Holiday Inn, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - New Year's Eve Rates, 1957-1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - New York City General Labor Council, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - New York Labor Management Council of Health aUndated Welfare Plans, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - New York State Council, HERE, 1971-1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - New York State Division of Human Rights, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - New York State Division of Human Rights: Elba de Sierra v. New York Hilton et al., 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - New York State Division of Human Rights: Mary Muzyka v. Hotel Regency et al., 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Night Shift Differential, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Night Shift Differential, 1970-1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Occupancy Tax, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Occupancy Tax and Promotion Cutbacks, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Occupational Outlook Handbook: Hotels, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - OPEIU, Local 153, 1953-1976 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - OPEIU, Local 153, 1977-1986 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Organizing Leaflets, 1930s (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Organizing Leaflets, 1940s-1960s (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Ottley, Peter, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - ParJays Restaurant, 1970-1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Pensioners Society, Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Pension Fund, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Pension Fund, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Pension Fund, 1981-1986 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Pension Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Pension Fund: Louglos case, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Pension Fund: Park South Hotel vs. HTC, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Pension Fund: Local 6 Employees, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Pension Fund: Rate Dispute, 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Pension Fund: Trustees, 1952-1957 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Pension Plan, 1952-1953 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Pension Plan, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Pension Reciprocity Report, Undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Pensioners Society, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Political Activity, 1961-1982 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Political Education Committee, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1947-1954 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1954-1982 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - "Puerto Rican Employment in NYC Hotels": Report, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Puerto Rico: Industry Committee Public Hearing Transcript, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Real Estate: Purchase, Lease, etc., 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Reapportionment (Federal), 1965 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Realty Hotels, Inc., Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Report: HTC Structure, Undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Report: V. Kamaras, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Restaurants, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Retired Hotel Employee Center, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Retired Hotel Employee Center, 1973-1981 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Rustin, Bayard, Undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Scholarships, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Seamen's Church Institute, 1967-1977 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Seamen's Church Institute, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Seamen's Institute Surveys, Undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Service Employees International Union, Local 32B, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Sexual Harrasment, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Shea and Gould, 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Shop Committee Meetings, 1983-1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Shop List, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Smith and Wollensky's, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Walter, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Smoking, Undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Staff Insurance Fund, 1958; 1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Staff Insurance Fund, 1978-1981 (Box 18, Folder 12A)
  - Staff List, Undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Star Cleaning Contractors, Inc., 1970 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Stevens, J. P., 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Stork Club Strike, 1957-1965 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Strike, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Tag Operating, Inc. and HTC: Arbitrations, 1969-1972 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Tax Deduction, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Taxes: General, 1953-1963 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Theater District, Undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Thirty-Five-Hour Work Week, 1959-1964 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Tips, 1956-1963 (Box 18, Folder 23A)
  - Tips, 1964-1976 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Tips: Bellman, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Tips: New York State Hotels, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Tips: Social Security, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Transport Workers, Undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Twenty Fifth Anniversary: Journal and Pageant Script, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Union Family Medical Fund, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Union Family Medical Fund, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Union Family Medical Fund, 1977-1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Union Family Medical Fund: Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - United Farm Workers, undated (Box MSOS003, Folder 1)
  - United Jewish Appeal, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - U.S. District Court: Grand Jury Investigation Documents re: Café Ziegfeld and Picadilly Hotel, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - U.S. District Court: Grand Jury Investigation Documents Submitted to Bruce Baird, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - U.S. v. John Doe: Materials, 1981-1985 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - U.S. v. Persico: Exhibits 360, 361, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - U.S. v. Persico: Indictment and Other Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - U.S. v. Persico: Nolle Prosequi, Falanga/Pitta, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - U.S. v. Persico: Notes, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - U.S. v. Persico: Transcripts, 1981-1985 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - U.S. v. Persico: Transcripts 5331-6513 (not complete), 1986 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - U.S. v. Persico: Transcripts 13569-15001 (not complete), 1986 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - U.S. v. Persico: Transcripts, Shaw Version (1of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - U.S. v. Persico: Transcripts, Shaw Version (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - U.S.v. Persico: Trial Prep, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Valentino's Lease, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Wage Increases, 1954-1958 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Wage Negotiations, 1957-1962 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Wage Policy Committee, 1964-1979 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Wertheim Assets Management Services, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Workers Compensation, 1952-1965 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Worlds Fair, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1967-1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - YMCA (Capitol), 1956 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - YMCA Stone House, 1966,1982-1988 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - YMCA (West Side "Y"), 1966-1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA), Undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - YWCA, 1964-1969 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - YWCA, 1970-1980 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Series IV: Hotel Files, circa 1930-1986
  Series IV: Hotel Files, 1930s-1986. In this series various kinds of material: membership records, dues records, grievances, correspondence, organizing and bargaining materials, and general historical material is grouped together under the name of each individual hotel.
  - General, Undated; 1913; 1962; 1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Card File A-C, 1940s-1950s (Box 21, Folder 1a)
  - Card File D-H, 1940s-1950s (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Card File K-P, 1940s-1950s (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Card File R-W, 1940s-1950s (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1937-1945 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Abbey, 1942-1943 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Abbey: Organizing, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Abbey: Victoria, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Adams: Dues, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Adams: Leaflets, Undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Adams: Organizing, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Airport Hilton: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Alamac, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Alamac: Dues, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Albert, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Albert: Dues, 1941-1944 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Alden, 1940-1943 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Alden: Dues, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Algonquin, 1939-1985 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Algonquin: Dues, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Algonquin: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Algonquin: Leaflets, Undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Allerton House: Leaflets, 1950s (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Ambassador (Sheraton East), 1939-1968 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Ambassador: Leaflets, 1930s-1940s (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - America, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Americana, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Americana, Undated; 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Ansonia, Undated; 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Ansonia: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Ansonia: Leaflets, Undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Astor, 1939-1967 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Astor: Dues, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Astor: Leaflets, 1940s-1950s (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Bancroft, Undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Barbizon, 1976-1986 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Barbizon Plaza, Undated; 1952-1985 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Barbizon Plaza: Leaflets, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Barclay, Undated; 1984 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Barclay: Dues, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Barclay: Leaflets, Undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Beacon, 1940-1969 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Beacon: Leaflets, Undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Beaux Arts: Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Bedford: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Bedford: Leaflets, Undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Beekman Tower, 1954-1985 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Belleclair, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Belmont Plaza, Undated; 1939-1945 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Belmont Plaza: Dues, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Belvedere, 1941-1944 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Berkley, Undated; 1944 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Berkshire, 1942-1985 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Beverly: Correspondence, 1977-1985 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Beverly: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Biltmore, 1939-1985 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Biltmore: Dues, Jan-Apr 1943 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Biltmore: Dues, Jul-Dec 1943 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Biltmore Valet: Dues, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Bing and Bing, Undated; 1939 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Blackstone, 1943-1985 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Blackstone: Dues, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Blackstone: Layoffs, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Bolivar, 1940-1943 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Bolivar: Dues, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Bolivar: Dues, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Bolivar: Leaflets, Undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Bossert, 1940-1975 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Bossert: Dues, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Bossert: Leaflets, 1953-1962 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Bradford: Leaflets, Undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Bretton Hall, 1937-1954 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Bretton Hall: Dues, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Brevoort, 1952-1953 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Brevoort: Dues, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Brewster, 1937-1973 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Brewster: Dues, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Brewster: Dues, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Brewster: Leaflets, Undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Bristol, 1937-1965 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Brittany, 1937-1965 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Brittany: Dues, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Broadmoor, 1937-1954 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Broadmoor: Dues, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Broadway Central, 1940-1973 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Broadway Central: Dues, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Bryant, 1940-1976 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Bryant: Dues, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Buckingham, Undated; 1939-1943 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Buckingham: Dues, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Buckingham: Dues, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Cambridge House, 1951-1966 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Cameron, 1937-1944 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Capitol, Undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Carlton House, 1951-1984 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Carlyle, 1944-1980 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Carlyle, 1981-1985 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Carriage House, 1964-1974 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Carteret, 1937-1944 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Century, 1939-1964 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Century: Dues, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Chalfonte, 1952-1969 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Chalfonte: Dues, 1943-1944 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Chateau Madrid, 1950-1954 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Chatham, 1954, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Chelsea, 1937-1969 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Chesterfield, 1937-1944 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - City Squire, 1963-1977 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Claridge, 1937-1953 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Clifton House, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Clifton House: Leaflets, Undated (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Collingwood, 1946-1985 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Commodore, 1937-1978 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Commodore: Dues, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Commodore: Dues, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Commodore: Leaflets, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Concourse Plaza, 1943-1976 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Concourse Plaza: Dues, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Continental, 1959, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Cornish Arms, 1937-1978 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Cornish Arms: Dues, 1964-1977 (Box 23, Folder 32)